permanentstyle.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy – Permanent Style

At Permanent Style ([www.permanentstyle.com)](https://www.permanentstyle.com/), one of our top priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document describes the types of information that are collected and recorded by Permanent Style and how we use them. If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at [info@permanentstyle.co.uk](mailto:info@permanentstyle.com)

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

We are a Data Controller of your information.

Permanent Style's legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the personal information we collect and the specific context in which we collect the information, i.e. because:

  * Permanent Style needs to perform a contract with you

  * You have given Permanent Style permission to do so

  * Processing your personal information is in Permanent Style's legitimate interests

  * and Permanent Style needs to comply with the law

Permanent Style will retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have particular data protection rights. If you wish to be informed what personal information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please [contact us](mailto:info@permanentstyle.com).

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  * The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.

  * The right of rectification.

  * The right to object.

  * The right of restriction.

  * The right to data portability

  * and The right to withdraw consent

## Information we collect

This section details the information we may collect about you.

  * Basic personal details, such as name, email address and IP address. These details are only collected if you optionally sign up to our mailing list. Read more about this below in the section titled 'Third party services and your data'.

  * Your activity on our website: Permanent Style follows a standard procedure of using log files and analytics software to obtain an understanding about our visitors actions on this website. The information collected by log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is analysing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements on the website, and gathering demographic information.

## Cookies and web beacons

Permanent Style uses 'cookies'. The cookies we use are limited to the following:

  * Google Analytics: we use this third-party service to assist us in understanding the usage of our site, where visitors are from, what kind of the device they use and what pages they interact with.

  * WordPress: the website is built with WordPress and this includes some basic non-personal tracking-data cookies that assist with displaying the correct content for you.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. For more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, see the browsers' respective websites.

## Third-party services and your data

We may use the following third-party service providers to process and store your data:

  *   * Google LLC: We use the Google Analytics service to measure the performance of this website.

  * Automattic, Inc: we use WordPress software (and associated add-ons) to manage the content of this website.

  * SiteGround Spain SL: we use SiteGround for providing web hosting services.

## Children's information

Another high priority is additional protection for children using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity. Permanent Style does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to [contact us](mailto:info@permanentstyle.com) and we will do our best to promptly remove such information from our records.

## Online privacy policy only

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Permanent Style. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
